<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on WHISTLER.PAGE</title><link>https://whistler.page/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on WHISTLER.PAGE</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://whistler.page/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>NEW! v0.1.3 is now available!</title><link>https://whistler.page/post/new-v013-now-available/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whistler.page/post/new-v013-now-available/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s this, now? I finally finished getting back into the swing of things, and build v0.1.3 is available to read now!
More to follow obviously (v0.1.4 is next), but I&amp;rsquo;m starting to get on a roll!
[ READ RCP ]</description></item><item><title>Systemware Monthly Progress Report</title><link>https://whistler.page/post/systemware-progress-report-1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whistler.page/post/systemware-progress-report-1/</guid><description>Header The time: 3:27 PM Eastern Time
The place: Systemware Internal Product Testing Lab 3
The writer: Jay Isles
Summary This is the first of a monthly internal progress report used for tracking the movements of the sapient AI, Whistler. During the course of the month, Whistler has not moved in much, if any, capacity. The only occurance to have happened within the month is a single update to its so-called &amp;ldquo;pet project&amp;rdquo;, Dreamsearch.</description></item><item><title>A Minor Update</title><link>https://whistler.page/post/minor-update-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whistler.page/post/minor-update-1/</guid><description>Small things to big things, eh? Hello!
I just now cleaned house with my websites. Specifically, their about pages should be nice and neat now (both here, on my Catalog page, and on the spicy variant).
I&amp;rsquo;ve fully come to terms with the fact that I need not drop my projects, even if it takes me forever to finish them. That&amp;rsquo;s honestly been the hard part, just sticking with something! It&amp;rsquo;s also why RCP was dropped for so long&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Returning from the Crypt of the Past...</title><link>https://whistler.page/post/return-crypt-past/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whistler.page/post/return-crypt-past/</guid><description>What are you doing now? I just put up an old story I made ages ago, or more specifically two parts of.
RCP is something I intend to make into a bit of a horror story, but progress is somewhat slow!
I&amp;rsquo;d know, since it stalled for a year, but now I&amp;rsquo;m working on it again. I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to pull it out of the freezer for a while now, but my past self just had to generate it with Microsoft Word.</description></item><item><title>The Modern Internet</title><link>https://whistler.page/post/the-modern-internet/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 18:54:02 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://whistler.page/post/the-modern-internet/</guid><description>&lt;p>First instance of me using this site as a bit of a blog, yay. Why not use Twitter? Reddit? Literally anything else? Oh boy, strap in.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Dreamsearch Announcement</title><link>https://whistler.page/post/dreamsearch-announcement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://whistler.page/post/dreamsearch-announcement/</guid><description>Dreamsearch If you are receiving this message, please do not panic. You are asleep, and everything is working normally. This pre-written message will help you get situated with the Dreamsearch project.
You may be wondering why you cannot see. This is normal. Due to the limitations of $CURRENT_TECHNOLOGY, visuals and auditory information cannot be generated. To counteract this, Systemware(R) has created the Systemware Intelligent System Software, or SWISS, to assist you.</description></item><item><title>Happy birthday, Penny!</title><link>https://whistler.page/post/penny-bday/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 17:21:19 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://whistler.page/post/penny-bday/</guid><description>This was a terrible post celebrating a friend&amp;rsquo;s birthday. I wiped it because it was terrible. I left the page here so the funny QR code still works.</description></item></channel></rss>